Week 12. Day 1. The Leaning Tower of Pisa. Leaning. Sight. Vertical. Be supposed to.
Foundation. Take some time off. Leave alone. Tilt. Chamber. Lead. Stabilize. Day 2. A house
full of junk. Full of. Bear. Childhood. Outdated. Emergency. Hoard. Part with. Possession. Enormous.
Disorganized. Fill up with. Be recognized as. Participate. Day 3. Magic Realism. Concept.
Tactic. Realism. Come from. Be associated with. Fantasy. Supernatural. Setting. Critic. Out-of-date. Racism. Genre.
Play an important role. Merge. Light fiction. Day 4. Charlie Chaplin. A serious man. Expressive. Waddle. Nazi. Urge. Antics. Dictator.
Climax. Democracy. Authorities. Harass. Oppose. Ashamed. Day 5. Dissertification.
Agriculture. Biodiversity. Drought. Farm. Erode. Overgrace. Ecosystem. Restore. Do. Degrade.
Reforestation. Solution. Day 6. Look away from the light. Reak. Havoc. Cycle. Give off. Wavelength.
Favor. Match. Brightness. Similarity. Melatonin. Disturb. Shift. Diabetes. Powerless. Block out.